(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
重大会告
[Title: Major Announcement]
新3Dお披露目日
[Title: New 3D Reveal Date]
博衣こより生誕Live 2026
ゲーミングソングLive
[Title: Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026
Gaming Song Live]
クワッ！こよりだよ！
Kua! It's Koyori!
せーの！こくよべ！
Ready! Shout Koyo-be!
はい！#こより実験中 です！
Yes! Hashtag #KoyoriExperimenting!
オーケー！こよはー
Okay! Koyo is—
ずっと！ずっと！どうですか！
Always! Always! How are you!
はい！やったー！
Yes! I did it!
#こよりスケッチ テレレ〜ン！
#KoyoriSketch Ta-da!
はい！ほえ！せーの！
Yes! Hoe! Ready, go!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
勉強晒し時間！
Time to study!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！実験時間！
Uwa! Experiment time!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こよりの朝食はネーム！
Koyori's breakfast is a draft!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！ヘルプ！
Uwa! Help!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！お勉強！
Uwa! Studying!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
嘘なんでね！見当た！
That was a lie! I saw you!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
可愛いでーす！てやー！
I'm cute! Te-ya!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
オッケー！こくよべ！
Okay! Shout Koyo-be!
さあー！やったー！
Now then! I did it!
やったー！間に合ったー！
Yatta! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみにすだちは茎です
By the way, sudachi is a stalk
はい！お肉！全般！
Yes! Meat! In general!
冷凍うどんは常備してます
I always have frozen udon in stock
どうですか？はい！やったー！
How is it? Yes! I did it!
証明完了 Q.E.D.
Proof complete, Q.E.D.!
私の戦闘力は54万です
My power level is 540,000
助手君はシュークリームです
Joshu-kun is a cream puff
ポメラニアン少々だよ
Just a little bit of Pomeranian
竹の子派です。嘘つき！
I'm on Team Takenoko. Liar!
ワー！150 50！
Wah! 150 50!
焼酎は飲み物ではありません
Shochu is not a drink
豚骨ラーメン！イエーイ！
Tonkotsu ramen! Yay!
尻尾もフリフリだめです
Wagging my tail is also no good
みんなの応援が必要だよ！
I need everyone's support!
[博衣こより生誕Live 2026]
[Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026]
マヨネーズ マヨネーズ
Mayonnaise, Mayonnaise
こよ...
Koyo...
こよりは マヨネーズで 回復した
[Koyori recovered with mayonnaise]
助手くんが仲間になった！
[Assistant-kun joined the party!]
AIこよりが仲間になった！
[AI Koyori joined the party!]
もふこよが仲間になった！
[Mofukoyo joined the party!]
へい! カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Hey! Like the morning sun shining on Kalos,
(ニトロチャージ熱く行こうぜ)
(Let's go with a hot nitro charge!)
さあ! 進もうぜ いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's move forward, we're always ready!
(かたやぶりへんげんじざいで)
(With our unconventional, ever-changing style!)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
With our overlapping feelings synchronized,
決して消えない絆になるから
It becomes a bond that will never fade away.
どこまでも強くなれる
Because we can become stronger forever,
俺たちならwoh woh woh yeah
If it's us, woh woh woh yeah!
いくZ!! 激しく燃えるバトル
Go!! A fierce and burning battle,
いくZ!! ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Go!! A crisis is an opportunity,
いこうZ!! きしかいせい
Go!! A comeback!
絶対に諦めない
We will never give up,
俺たちは諦めない
We will never give up!
へい! 例えどんな壁が道を塞いだって
Hey! No matter what wall is blocking our path,
(いつでも当たって砕けろで)
(Always hit it and break it!)
さあ! この手でしょうりのほしを掴むんだ
Come on! Grab the star of victory with these hands,
(折れないふくつのこころで)
(With an unyielding heart.)
俺たちはいつでもどんな時も
Because we are always connected
同じ心で繋がってるから
by the same heart at all times,
何度でも立ち上がるぜ
I can stand up again and again,
お前となら
if I'm with you.
いくZ!! 手強いライバルたち
Go!! Formidable rivals,
いくZ!! 決めろいちげきひっさつ!
Go!! Decide with one blow, sure kill!
いこうZ!! 負けられない
Go!! We can't lose,
思いがここにあるから
because the determination is here,
夢がおれにはあるから
because I have a dream.
博衣こよみ生誕ライブ2026見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to the Haku Koyori Birthday Live 2026!
神ゲーたちの神ゲームソングをいっぱい詰め込んでるの。
I've packed in lots of great songs from great games.
最後まで楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy until the very end!
いくZ!! 勝ちも負ける痛みも
Go!! The pain of winning and losing,
いくZ!! なんでも分け合える
Go!! We can share anything,
いこうZ!! 仲間がいる
Go!! We have friends,
俺たちは一人じゃない!
we are not alone!
いくZ!! 激しく燃えるバトル
Go!! A fierce and burning battle,
いくZ!! ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Go!! A crisis is an opportunity,
いこうZ!! きしかいせい
Go!! A comeback,
絶対に諦めない
never give up!
いくZ!! 譲れない夢がある
Go!! I have a dream I won't give up,
いくZ!! 必ずゲットだぜ
Go!! I'll definitely get it,
いこうZ!! 手を伸ばして
Go!! Reach out,
いつか描いた未来へ
to the future I once imagined,
誰も知らない高みへ
to heights no one knows.
さあ! 上げてくぜ(100万ボルト)
Come on! Let's raise it (a million volts!)
そう! 立ち向かって共に行こうぜ
Yes! Let's stand up and go together,
見たことのない夢の向こうまで
to the other side of our dreams that we've never seen before.
はーい！みんな、こんこよ！
Hi, everyone! Kon-koyo!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよ！
I'm Haku Koyori, the brains of Secret Society holoX from hololive 6th generation!
改めて今日は、博衣こより生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you so much for coming to the Haku Koyori Birthday Live 2026 today!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう！イェイ！
Thank you for all the comments too! Yay!
「カッコいい」？見えてるよ、ありがとう！
"Cool"? I can see that, thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショは...
So, please post your impressions and screenshots of the live...
#博衣こよみ生誕ライブ2026 をつけてたくさん呟いてね！
using the hashtag #HakuKoyoriBirthdayLive2026!
ポストしてください！
Please post about it!
目指せトレンド1位、よろしくだー！
Aim for #1 trending, please!
はい、ということでちょっと息が整ってないですけど
Alright, so I'm a bit out of breath, but...
さて、今年の生誕ライブテーマは
anyway, this year's birthday live theme is...
『ゲームソングライブ』です！
"Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた実況配信で一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや
Songs from the games we played together in past streams and shared memories of,
こよりが大好きなゲーム関連の楽曲をたくさん詰め込みました。
and many songs from games that I personally love.
最後まで全力で楽しんでいってねー！
Enjoy it with all your might until the end!
ということで、1曲目は大好きなポケモンのXYZを歌わせていただきました！ねー！
So, for the first song, I sang XYZ from my favorite Pokemon! Right!
しゅくー！あー！
Bam! Ah!
「俺はこいつと旅に出る」っていうことです。はい。
"I'm going on a journey with this guy," as they say. Yes.
Xでセトリ予想もね、みんなにたくさんしてもらってたんですけど
I had everyone predict the setlist on X,
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったけど
and while there were many Pokemon predictions,
XYZ当てられてる人は結構少なかったです。
very few people actually guessed XYZ.
当たった君、おめでとう！
Congrats to those who got it right!
ま、この曲は、ま、ZAが発売になったっていうのもあるんですけど
Well, this song, partly because Pokémon Legends: Z-A was announced,
歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもぴったりな曲なので選びました。
but the lyrics are so good and it's actually perfect for me, so I chose it.
さあ、この後も自分の予想が当たってるかなーって
Now, please keep enjoying while wondering if your predictions will come true,
ドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください。
filled with excitement.
新3Dお披露目もあるからね！絶対に最後まで見てってね！
There's also a new 3D reveal! Make sure to watch until the end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲、ゲームの世界へ、どうぞ！
Now then, it's about time for the next song. Into the game world, here you go!
[キャラ選択画面]
[Character Selection Screen]
[アンロック！]
[Unlock! ????]
気がついたら同じ面ばかりプレイ
When I realize it, I'm playing the same level,
そしていつも同じ場所で死ぬ
and I always die in the same place.
諦めずに消える足場に挑戦するけど
I don't give up and try the disappearing platforms, but
すぐに下に落ちるよ
I fall right down.
アイテム2号があれば楽に向こうの岸まで着くけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman!
あの竜巻何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try to avoid that tornado, I can't.
うしろに回って撃ち続けてもいずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I go behind and keep shooting, eventually I get blown away by the wind.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I tried hitting the button repeatedly, but
竜巻相手じゃ意味が無い
it's useless against the tornado.
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, next time, to win for sure,
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Can until the very end.
気がついたらライフももう少ししかない
When I realize it, I have only a little life left,
そしていつもそこでE缶使う
and I always use my E-Can there.
諦めずにエアーマンまでたどり着くけれど
I don't give up and reach Airman, but
すぐに残機なくなる
I immediately run out of lives.
リーフシールドがあれば楽にエアーマンを倒せるけど
If I had the Leaf Shield, I could easily defeat Airman, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
ウッドマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Woodman!
落ちる木の葉は何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try to avoid the falling leaves, I can't.
後に下がって距離をとってもいずれは距離を詰められる
Even if I step back and keep my distance, eventually I get cornered.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I tried hitting the button repeatedly, but
あいつのジャンプはくぐれない
I can't get past his jumps.
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, next time, to win for sure,
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Can until the very end.
アイテム2号があれば楽に向こうの岸まで着くけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman!
あの竜巻 何回やっても避けれない
That tornado, no matter how many times I try, I can't avoid it.
後ろに回って 撃ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I go around to the back and keep shooting, eventually I'll be blown away.
タイム連打も ためしてみたけど 竜巻相手じゃ 意味がない！
I tried button mashing, but it's useless against the tornado!
だから次は絶対勝つために 僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
So, to win for sure next time, I'll save my E-Tank until the very end.
倒せないよ…
I can't defeat him...
ロボのテーマ
[Title: Robo's Theme]
カエルのテーマ
[Title: Frog's Theme]
Melodies of Life
[Title: Melodies of Life]
あてもなく さまよっていた
I was wandering aimlessly.
手がかりもなく 探しつづけた
I kept searching, though I had no clues.
あなたがくれた 思い出を
The memories you gave me...
心をいやす 歌にして
...into a song to heal my heart.
…詩にして
...into a song.
約束もすることもなく
Without making promises,
交わす言葉も決めたりもせず
without deciding what words to say,
抱きしめ、そして確かめた
you held me, and then I was certain
日々は二度と帰らぬ
that those days would never return.
記憶の中の手を振るあなたは
You, waving your hand in my memories,
わたしの名を呼ぶことが出来るの？
can you call out my name?
あふれるその涙を
Turn those overflowing tears
輝く勇気にかえて
into glittering courage.
いのちはつづく
Life goes on,
夜を越え
across the night,
疑うことのない明日へとつづく
and continues to a certain tomorrow.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
Toward the sky beyond the flying birds,
いくつの記憶預けただろう
how many memories were entrusted?
儚い希望も夢も
Short-lived hopes and dreams
届かぬ場所に忘れて
are forgotten in an unreachable place.
めぐり逢うのは偶然と言えるの？
Can you say our meeting was a coincidence,
別れる時が必ず来るのに
even though the time to part will surely come?
消えゆく運命でも
Even though fate is fleeting,
君が生きている限り
as long as you live,
いのちはつづく
life goes on,
永遠に
eternally,
その力の限りどこまでも
to anywhere, as long as you're strong.
わたしが死のうとも
Though I may die,
君が生きている限り
as long as you live,
いのちはつづく
life goes on,
永遠に
eternally,
その力の限りどこまでもつづく
it continues to anywhere, as long as you're strong.
きみの瞳に映る
The color of what is reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color is it?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう陽の光を
I will bestow upon you the sunlight.
キミガタメ / 作詞：須谷尚子 作曲：下川直哉
[Song: Kimi ga Tame / Lyrics: Naoko Sutani / Music: Naoya Shimokawa]
悲しみが溢れ
Sorrow overflowed,
瞼閉じました
and I closed my eyelids.
こぼれた滴は
The spilled drops
心に沁みゆく
sink into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The spreading waves
弱く交えます
are weak, interacting.
とどけしゆりかご
Passing on the cradle,
眠りをさそう夢に
inviting sleep, to a dream.
なつかし 面影を
Searching for nostalgic images,
さがす手を伸ばし
I reached out my hand...
強く 抱きしめたくなる
and strongly wanted to embrace you.
きみの瞳に映る
The color of what is reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color is it?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo,
渡そう高き空を
I will bestow upon you the high sky.
不安定な神様 / 作詞：須谷尚子 作曲：下川直哉
[Song: Fuantei na Kamisama / Lyrics: Naoko Sutani / Music: Naoya Shimokawa]
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
repeated meetings and partings.
また逢えるその日まで
Until the day we meet again,
解きかける旅人
a traveler beginning to unravel.
あなたが泣いている
You are crying,
ながるる涙の雨
a rain of flowing tears.
泣くなどとは言わない 心悲しくて
I won't say I've lost you, my heart is so sad.
生きとし生けるもの
Fragile living things,
何かを背負いながら
while carrying something.
見えない鎖に繋がれている
Are tied together by invisible chains.
どれほど救われただろう
How much was I saved,
あどけない笑顔を
by that innocent smile?
無くしたくはない
I don't want to lose it.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返すこと見ない
without seeing a repeat.
生まれてそして死んでいく宿命
The fate of being born and then dying.
かけ違えた世界で
In a world where things went wrong,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
repeated meetings and partings.
また逢えるその日まで
Until the day we meet again,
解きかける旅人
a traveler beginning to unravel.
戦闘開始!!
[Visual Text: Battle Start!!]
歪なこの心
This distorted heart,
黒く染めゆきながら
while being dyed black,
抑えられなくて 解き放たれる
unable to be suppressed, it is unleashed.
何遍名を呼んだだろう
How many times did I call your name?
あどけない笑顔は
The innocent smile
もうどこにもない
is nowhere to be found anymore.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
引き継いだ夢と愛を
Inherited dreams and love,
育て守り託しゆく運命
Destined to grow, protect, and entrust,
掛け違えた世界で
In a world where things have gone wrong,
探すたび引き裂かれても
Even if we are torn apart whenever we search,
また会えると信じて
I believe we can meet again,
時かける旅人
A time-traveling traveler.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す過去と未来
Repeating the past and the future,
生まれそして死んでゆく運命
Destined to be born and die,
掛け違えた世界で
In a world where things have gone wrong,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
Repeating encounters and partings,
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
A time-traveling traveler.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
A time-traveling traveler.
はい、ということで、Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきましたー！
Yes! And so, Suara-san joined us, and we performed together!
Suaraさん、自己紹介を頂いてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, could you please introduce yourself?
はい、Suaraです。うたわれるものシリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です。
Yes, I'm Suara. I sing many of the theme songs for the Utawarerumono series.
はい！ようこそー！
Yes! Welcome!
こよりさーん！
Koyori-san!
そうなんです。実はですね、うたわれるものというゲーム、昨年約3ヶ月間かけてシリーズの三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれども...
That's right. Actually, I streamed a let's-play of the Utawarerumono trilogy over about three months last year...
そのうたわれるもの、本当に曲がめちゃくちゃいいのですが...
Utawarerumono has such incredible music, but...
その歌をほぼ全てSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃるというのです！
Suara-san is the one singing almost all of those songs!
はい。
Yes.
もう耳が本当に幸せで...
My ears were just so happy...
いや、こちらこそですよ本当に。
No, the pleasure was all mine, really.
もう恐縮、恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、ありがとうございます！
I'm so humbled and overwhelmed, but thank you so much!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
Suaraさんには、実は4周年の時に逆凸でメッセージもちょうだいしておりまして...
Actually, I received a message from Suara-san during a reverse-call on my 4th anniversary...
その時に、いつか一緒に歌いたいというのも、こよりも結構熱烈なラブコールをさせていただいていたんですけれども...
At that time, I sent a very passionate "love call" saying I wanted to sing with you someday...
その思いを本日叶えることができました！
And today, I was able to make that wish come true!
え、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけれども...
Um, I have a few questions for you...
実は、あの、うたわれるものの実況してた時に...
Actually, when I was streaming Utawarerumono...
最終回で、Suaraさんがコメントしてくださりまして...
In the final episode, Suara-san left a comment...
はい、あの、こよりの実況をご覧くださったと思うんですけれども...
Yes, I believe you watched my let's-play stream...
見られますか、実況とかって普段？
Do you usually watch let's-plays?
いや、ちょっと実はですね、初めて拝見させていただいて...
Actually, to be honest, it was the first time I'd ever seen one...
えー！そうなんですか！
Eh! Is that so?!
そうなんですよ。あの、まあ、えーと、アクアプラスのね、スタッフの方とかからも...
Yes. Um, well, staff from AquaPlus and others...
こよりさんっていう、うたわれ配信してるよって言って、情報を聞いていたんですよね。
They told me, "Someone named Koyori-san is streaming Utawarerumono."
で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも、ぜひ見てみてくださいって言って。
And my fans at my live concerts also said, "You should definitely check her out."
それで、見させていただいたっていうのが、あ、最終回だったんですけれども。
So, the first one I watched was the final episode.
そうだったんですね。恐縮ですが...
I see. I'm so honored...
いやもう、すごい、本当に、こう、こよりさんのうたわれるものへの愛がすごい溢れてて...
No, really, Koyori-san's love for Utawarerumono was just overflowing...
本当に見てて、もう最後までずっと見させていただいて。
I watched it all the way through to the end.
で、あ、コメント送りたいなー、あ、でももう早くしないと終わっちゃう、と思いながら...
And I thought, "I want to comment," but also "I have to hurry or it'll end!"
で、あの、同じ部屋に、私の息子がいたんですけれども。
And my son was in the same room at the time.
おー、息子さんまで！
Oh, even your son!
息子に、コメント、ちょっと送ってみていいと思う？って聞いて。
I asked him, "Do you think it's okay if I send a comment?"
そしたら、いいんちゃう？って言って。
And he said, "Why not?"
いい息子さんだー！
What a good son!
それで、もう、本当に震える手でコメント打って...
So, with my hands literally shaking, I typed the comment...
もう、あ、早く、もうエンターキーをこう...
Thinking, "Quick, I have to hit the Enter key..."
そんな緊張してくださったんですか！
You were that nervous?!
押そうか、押そうか、どうしよう、でも、はよう押さな、みたいな感じで...
I kept thinking, "Should I press it? I have to press it now!"
はい。それで、もうドキドキしながら、あの送らせていただいたら...
Yes. And so, while my heart was pounding, when I sent that message...
スアラさんね、あの、コメント気づいてくださって。
Suara-san noticed the comment.
もうとっても嬉しかったです。こよりもですし、見てた助手くんたちも...
I was so happy. Koyori was too, and the Assistants watching were also...
ものすごく、もう嬉しくて。やっぱり、あの、見ていただけるっていうのが...
Incredibly, just so happy. After all, the fact that you were watching us...
スアラさんとか、アクアプラスさんもそうですし、その、公式の皆様に...
Like Suara-san, and also Aquaplus, for the official people to...
ご覧いただけるって本当に嬉しく恐縮なことなので、もう、幸せでございました。
View our stream is truly a happy and humbling thing; I was so happy.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you so much.
もうすごい楽しくて見入っちゃいました、本当に。嬉しいーっす。
It was so fun that I was glued to the screen, really. I'm so happy.
すごい長時間ね、されてるのがすごいなと思って。本当に、はい。
I thought it was amazing how you were doing it for so long. Truly.
もうそのあとの夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたり、すごい体力だなーって...
I even listened to the singing stream later that night, and thought, "What stamina..."
思いながら、はい。楽しんでるのね。うたわれるものが本当に素晴らしい作品だったから。
While thinking that, yes. You enjoyed it. Utawarerumono is such a wonderful work.
ですので、その、うたわれるものとずっと付き合っていらっしゃる...
So, Suara-san, you've been involved with Utawarerumono for a long time...
スアラさんですけれども、推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
But do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか。推しキャラはやっぱり...
A favorite character? Well, for my favorite character...
ちょっとエルルゥってことにしておかないと、ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれない。
I have to say Eluluu, or I might get stabbed with a fork.
あれ？もしからして、あの中の人...中の人の柚木涼香さんとね、
Oh? Could it be because you're close with the person inside, Ryoka Yuzuki-san?
とっても仲良くさせていただいてて。本当にあの、アニメの放送の時からですね、
We're very close. Really, ever since the anime broadcast,
2006年からずっと仲良くさせていただいてるっていう...
Since 2006, we've been close friends...
20年！そうですね、20年。すごい！
20 years! That's right, 20 years. Amazing!
それはエルルゥ推し...ですね。ということで、エルルゥ推しということで、お願いします。
Then you're an Eluluu fan. So with that, please consider me an Eluluu fan.
こよりはアルルゥが大好きなので、エルルゥ、アルルゥで、姉妹で！
Koyori loves Aruruu, so Eluluu and Aruruu, like sisters!
姉妹で！嬉しいです。
Sisters! I'm so happy.
はい、ということで、もっともっとお話ししたいんですけれども、お時間が来てしまいまして。
Yes, so, I'd like to talk much more, but we're out of time.
本当に今日は一緒に歌っていただき、ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for singing with me today!
ありがとうございました。こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、優しい、温かい声に...
Thank you. Koyori-san's truly soft, gentle, warm voice...
包まれながら、私も一緒に歌えて、本当に幸せでした。
Surrounded me, and being able to sing together, I was truly happy.
恐縮でございます。ありがとうございます。
I'm humbled. Thank you.
またぜひ、いろいろご一緒させていただける機会があれば嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if there's another chance for us to do things together.
ぜひぜひ、よろしくお願いします。ありがとうございました。
By all means, I look forward to it. Thank you very much.
ということで、スアラさんでした！ありがとうございましたー！
And that was Suara-san! Thank you so much!
こよりのリズムラボ
[Title: Koyori's Rhythm Lab]
9th リミックス
[Title: 9th Remix]
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
[Song: Eventually, a woman will become beautiful]
だいスキ！
Love it!
男に媚びての人生
A life of flattering men,
本当の自分に出会えない
I cannot meet my true self
あのね ダンスがSEXY
You know, dancing is SEXY,
君は いい女なんだ
you are a good woman
あのね キスしてCRAZY
You know, kissing is CRAZY,
君は まんまで素敵だよ
you are wonderful just as you are
輝きたい 愛されたい
I want to shine, I want to be loved
歴史がほおっておかない
History won't leave me alone,
華やか人生 生きたい
I want to live a glamorous life
Ah 悲しい歌 流れる
Ah, a sad song flows,
街の中歩く
walking through the city
涙が流れちゃう 涙が流れちゃう
I'm tearing up, I'm tearing up
涙が流れちゃうのは どうしてなんだろう
Why am I tearing up?
やがて女は きれいになるだろう
Eventually, a woman will become beautiful
だから 恋 破れて
So, if love is broken
誰も 信じられなきゃ
and you cannot trust anyone
泣きたいだけ泣けばいい
Then cry as much as you want
そして女は きれいになるだろう
And then a woman will become beautiful
だから また 恋して
So, fall in love again
時に 夢中すぎて まわりが見えなく なってもいいじゃない
Sometimes you're too absorbed, and you can't see what's around you, isn't that fine?
だいスキ！
Love it!
こっち見て！
Look over here!
Big Pink Coyote Muscles
[News: Big Pink Coyote Muscles]
だいスキ！
Love it!
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai Scream!
愛♡スクリ～ム！
[Song: Ai ♡ Scream!]
教えて！ もっとあなたの事
Tell me! More about yourself
Tell me more, more, more, more
聞かせて！ もっとあなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice
Let me hear more, more, more
こんなドキドキ もう抑え切れない
I can’t hold back this heart-pounding rush anymore
Oh! All I need you
Oh! All I need is you
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends; the fated version of me
見つけて欲しいの
I want you to find me
One：勇気を出して
One: Summoning my courage
Two：見つめる作戦
Two: My 'staring at you' plan
Three：瞳と目が合えば
Three: When our eyes finally meet
Fall：止められない
Fall: I just can’t be stopped
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this crush and this love
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
I’m melting away, melt, melty
ねぇ？ ねぇ？ ねぇ？ 気づいて "my darling"
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, "my darling"
届け！大好き！
I hope my love reaches you!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s shout it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
OK！
Okay!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s shout it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
こよりちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
マヨネーズよりも あ・な・た
More than mayonnaise, I love you
AZKiちゃん！
AZKi-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
こしあん つぶあん よりも あ・な・た
More than smooth or chunky bean paste, I love you
ラミィちゃん！
Lamy-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
お酒よりも あ・な・た
More than alcohol, I love you
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き こよラミあず
Of course we love Koyo-Lamy-Azu!
止められない
Nothing can stop me
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this crush and this love
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
I’m melting away, melt, melty
ねぇ？ ねぇ？ ねぇ？ 気づいて "my darling"
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, "my darling"
届け！大好き！
I hope my love reaches you!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s shout it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
OK！
Okay!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s shout it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
おねがい見つけて "my darling"
Please find me, "my darling"
おねがい気づいて "my darling"
Please notice me, "my darling"
One：勇気を出して
One: Summoning my courage
Two：近づく作戦
Two: My 'getting closer' plan
Three：手と手が触れて
Three: When our hands finally touch
Fall：止められない
Fall: Nothing can stop me now
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this crush and this love
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
I’m melting away, melt, melty
ねぇ？ ねぇ？ ねぇ？ 気づいて "my darling"
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, "my darling"
それは！アナタ！
It’s always been you!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s cry it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
OK！
Okay!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s cry it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s cry it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
OK！
Okay!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
Love, love, scream, scream, let’s cry it out
（スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！）
(Scream! Ice Cream!)
La la la la la love love
Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026
[Title: Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026]
あー！ 打ちまくり！
[Flare]: Ah! I'm hitting them all!
やばいやばい！
[Marine]: Oh no, oh no!
定位置、定位置！
[Koyori]: Regular position, regular position!
ガツーン！！
[Visual: WHAM!!]
よっしゃー！
[Koyori]: All right!
カッキーーン！！
[Marine]: Kakiin!!
ホームラン！
Home run!
え、え、待って、やばい、やばい！
[Marine]: Wait, wait, oh no, oh no!
カッキーーン！！
[Flare]: Kakiin!!
いけいけ！
[Flare]: Go, go!
打ちまくれー！
[Koyori]: Keep hitting them!
RELAY
[BGM: RELAY]
もう何十回も何百回も
Tens of times, hundreds of times...
澄む空見上げてたどり着いた場所が
I looked up at the clear sky and the place I reached
夢のダイヤモンド
is the diamond of my dreams.
何千回も何万回も
Thousands of times, tens of thousands of times,
涙流した君へ
to you who shed so many tears.
ねえ 諦められたことはあったけど
Hey, there were times I felt like giving up, but...
憧れは限界だったかな
Was my admiration at its limit?
もういらないよ
I don't need it anymore.
そこにただ待つなんて
Just waiting there...
もったいないでしょ
would be such a waste, right?
それぞれの物語
Our respective stories...
交差する瞬間を
at the moment they intersect,
見つめる君は
you who watches over them...
放つ夢だけ 大きな声出して
Let out a big voice for the dreams you release,
弾けそうな煌めきも
and the sparkling light that seems to burst.
消えることなく
Without ever fading away,
どこまででも
no matter how far,
世界に向こうに届けてよ
deliver them to the other side of the world.
終わることのない
An endless...
この胸の衝動は
impulse within this chest,
どうしても どうしても 僕を呼んでいたから
because no matter what, no matter what, it was calling out to me.
その先へと
Toward what lies ahead,
走り続ける
I'll keep on running,
次へ 次へ
to the next, and the next.
ヘイ！
Hey!
嘘だった中途半端な
The half-hearted lies...
不甲斐なさ抱えて
clutching that helplessness,
立ち尽くしていたあの日を 雨はプレリュード
standing still that day—the rain was a prelude.
何千回も何万回も
Thousands of times, tens of thousands of times,
挑み続けた君へ
to you who kept on challenging.
ねえ 聞かせてよ 夢はこんなんだったって
Hey, tell me... the dream was supposed to be like this.
諦めが簡単ならば
If giving up were easy,
絶対にないよ
then it definitely wouldn't exist.
誰に邪魔させようと
No matter who tries to stop us,
躊躇わないで
don't hesitate.
たくさんの情熱を
All of that passion,
落とさずつなげいく
keep it connected without dropping it,
そう 最後まで
yes, until the very end.
プライドに誓い 星を羽ばたいて
Vowing on our pride, taking flight to the stars,
鳴り止まないファンファーレ
an unceasing fanfare.
いつもここに
Always here,
流れていた
it has been flowing.
遠い未来へ 祈るように
Toward the distant future, like a prayer.
忘れられない
I can't forget
あの日々の後悔も
the regrets of those days either.
追いかけて 追いかけて 滑り込んだ この想い
Chasing, chasing, and sliding in with these feelings,
青い空に ふと溢れてた
they suddenly overflowed into the blue sky,
遠く 遠く
far, far away.
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
Waking up and repeating the cycle, to a sleepy morning
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し 胸を張って歩き出せる
When I pass through the classroom door, I can walk in with my chest puffed out proudly
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
Such a wind blows past everyday life
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I even thought I felt it
震え出す今この胸で
Now it starts to shake within my chest
もう来る気がした
I thought it would come soon
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
As those millions of stars vanished
見送った
I watched them fade
手を振った
I waved them good-bye
よかったね、と
I'm glad
手を振った
I waved my hand
よかったね、と
Saying, "I'm glad"
廊下の隅見下ろす
Looking down at the corner of the hallway
掃除の途中
While in the middle of cleaning
おかしなものだと思う
I think it's a strange thing
あたしの中の時は止まってるのに
Even though time within me has stopped
違う日々を生きてるように
It's like I'm living through different days
埃は雪のように降り積む
Dust piles up like snow
待ってる気がした
I felt like it was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling out
震え出す今この時が
Now, this very moment begins to tremble
見つけた気がした
I felt like I had found it
失われた記憶が呼び覚ました
The lost memories awakened
物語
A story...
永遠の
of eternal...
その終わり
endings.
いつの間にか駆けたしてた
Before I knew it, I was running
あなたに手を引かれてた
My hand was being pulled by you
昨日は遠く 明日はすぐ
Yesterday is far away, tomorrow is right there
そんな当たり前に心が踊った
My heart danced at such obviousness
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
震え出す今この胸で
Now, it begins to tremble in my chest
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was coming already
幾千の朝を越え 新しい陽が
Passing through thousands of mornings, a new sun...
待ってる気がした
...I felt was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling out
震えてるこの魂が
My soul is trembling
見つけた気がした
I felt like I had found it
幾億の夢のように消え去れる日を
The day that can vanish like billions of dreams
見送った
I saw it off
手を振った
I waved my hand
ありがとう、と
Saying, "Thank you"
ぽつり灯り 管制塔
A single light, the control tower
砂嵐の向こうへ
Beyond the sandstorm
祈るように綴った
I wrote as if in prayer
これからのこと
About the things to come
管制塔より
[Song: From the Control Tower]
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
お便り 届いていますか
Is my letter reaching you?
この世界がいつからか
I wonder when this world...
まるで他人事のように
...became like someone else's business
やけに静かなので
It's so strangely quiet
不安になったのです
That I became anxious
思い出したのです
I remembered
人知れず口を噤んだまま
While keeping my mouth shut in secret
終われないのです
I cannot let it end
それは嫌なのです
I hate that
夢ってもっと
Dreams were supposed to be...
わがままだったでしょう
...more selfish, weren't they?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, smile, notice me
此処に居るのにな、意地悪だな
I'm right here, you're being mean
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one
どうしたら、伝えられるのでしょう
How can I convey it?
どうしても、伝えたいよ
I want to convey it, no matter what
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
意気地無しなのでしょうか
Am I just a coward?
それともこの世界には
Or is it that in this world,
ぼくはお邪魔でしょうか
I'm just a nuisance?
だとしても綴るよ
Even so, I'll write.
みっともなく叫ぶよ
I'll scream ungracefully.
フラれたって好きだよ
Even if I'm rejected, I love you.
いいでしょ いいでしょ
Is that okay? Is it?
楽しかったよね
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は、嫌だ
I don't want to talk to myself anymore.
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
「別に待ってないよ」
"I wasn't waiting at all."
夢と呼んだそれもぼくだっただけ
It was just me who called it a dream.
もういいかい
Are you ready?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, smile at me, notice me.
此処に居るのにな、意地悪だな
I'm right here, you're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
The light that reaches no one...
ぼくだけは 光と呼び続ける
Only I will keep calling it light.
真夜中 管制塔から
In the middle of the night, from the control tower...
あなたを明かしてやる
I will illuminate you.
特報
[Special Announcement]
歌 博衣こよ
Vocals: Hakui Koyori
作詞・作曲 堀江晶太
Lyrics/Composition: Shota Horie
新アニメーションMV
New Animated Music Video
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, smile at me, notice me.
此処に居るのにな、意地悪だな
I'm right here, you're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
The light that reaches no one...
どうしたら、伝えられるのでしょう
How can I convey it?
どうしても、伝えたいよ
No matter what, I want to convey it.
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
[Premiere right after the live ends]
ということで、新曲のお披露目、フルアニメーションMV公開の告知、
So, we've had the new song reveal, the animated MV announcement,
新3Dのお披露目、3個どどーんとまとめてやらせていただきましたー！イエーイ！
and the new 3D reveal—all three at once! Yay!
情報量多かったけど、ついてこれてるかな？
It was a lot of info, but are you all keeping up?
はい、ちょっとね新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど、
Yes, I'm sure you're all distracted by how cute the new 3D is,
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください。
but first, let me talk about the original song.
お披露目させていただいたのは新曲『管制塔より』！
The new song I revealed is "Kanseitou yori"!
ついにあの堀江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
It was finally written for me by none other than Shota Horie!
みんな、どうだった？エモい？良かった？
How was it, everyone? Was it emotional? Did you like it?
はい、そしてですね今ちょっと映像も流して「すごい良い」って言ってくれててめっちゃ嬉しいんですけど、
I'm so happy to see everyone saying "it's great" while the video was playing,
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
but right after this live ends, the full animated MV will have its premiere!
多分もうマネちゃんがポチッとしてくれてると思います。
I think my manager has probably already clicked the button.
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわられている映像作品になっているので、
The video is a work of art with a lot of attention to its world-building,
何回も見て聞いて、そしてちょっと世界観の考察とかしてみてください。
so please watch and listen to it many times, and maybe try to analyze the setting a bit.
ちょっと待って1個言い忘れました。
Wait a second, I forgot one thing.
さっきの曲『管制塔より』、24時にリリースもあります！よろしくお願いします。
The song "Kanseitou yori" will also be released at midnight! Please check it out.
え、そしてお待たせしました、新3D！
And now, sorry for the wait—the new 3D!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛い？
How is it? Cute? Cute? Is it cute?
はい、もっとね話すことなく見せたいんだけど、
Yes, I want to just show it off without talking,
ももこママのいつものにすごい近くなったんじゃないかなと思います。
but I think it's become very close to Momoko-mama's original design.
この後のメン限ライブで撮影会もしまして、さらに細かく見せちゃうので、ぜひメン限ライブも来てください。
I'll be doing a photo session in the members-only live later to show it in more detail, so please come!
メン限ライブでは本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの、みんなが大好き曲、
In the members-only live, I'll also sing that song from the game everyone loves,
キンキンキンも歌うよ！お楽しみに。
the "Kin Kin Kin" song that I couldn't sing in the main stream! Look forward to it.
じゃあ1つだけ新3Dのめっちゃ変わったポイント教えちゃうと...
Well then, let me tell you just one point that's changed a lot in the new 3D...
ケモ耳が揺れます！うわー！可愛い！
The animal ears move! Wow! So cute!
2！
Two!
はい！ということでね！
Alright! And with that!
え、あ、あとトレンド1位も本当にありがとうございます！
Oh, and also, thank you so much for #1 on the trends!
今日無理かな～って思ってたんで、めっちゃ嬉しかったし
I thought it might be impossible today, so I'm really happy!
トレンド爆散！なんかすごいいっぱい入ってたみたいで
Trending explosion! It looks like so many tags got in!
本当にありがとう！
Thank you all so much!
それでは、もうひとつ大事なお知らせです！
Now then, I have one more important announcement!
ドン！
Ta-da!
博衣こより、誕生日記念グッズ2026が発売されます！イエーイ！
Hakuya Koyori Birthday Celebration Goods 2026 are going on sale! Yay!
早速詳細を見ていきましょう！
Let's check out the details right away!
まず1つ目はこちら！もふこよにもなれる！？2wayブランケット！
First up is this! The "Can also become Mofu-Koyo!?" 2-Way Blanket!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいるこよりの描き下ろしイラストです！
It features a new illustration of Koyori enjoying games in her room!
イラストはもちろんももこママ！
The illustration is, of course, by Momoko-mama!
これ丸めるともふこよに早変わりして、持ち運びも楽ちんだし
When rolled up, it quickly turns into Mofu-Koyo, making it easy to carry...
そのまま飾っても可愛いですね！
...and it's cute even if you just display it as is!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー～ゲーム実況編～！
Voice Keychain ~Game Commentary Edition~!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！こよりの録り下ろしボイスが入っているもので
The long-awaited voice keychain is here! It contains newly recorded voices of Koyori...
今回はライブに合わせてゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、
...and this time, to match the live theme, it has lines like a game commentary...
絶叫が6種類入っております！セリフはこよが考えました！
...including 6 types of screams! I thought up the lines myself!
イラストはなもり先生です！
The illustration is by Namori-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
Koyori Director Plushie Smartphone Stand!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよ！可愛い！
That "Koyori Director" has finally become a plushie! So cute!
そのまま飾るもよし、スマホスタンドにもなるので超便利です！
You can display it, and it also works as a phone stand, so it's super handy!
絶対ゲットしてね！
Be sure to get one!
最後はこちら！
And finally, this!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
Game Console-style Card Holder!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとかホロカも入れられて持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
It's a card holder for carrying things like the bonus bromide or Holocards!
中に入っている台紙のイラストはこよちゃんが描きました！
I drew the illustration on the backing card myself!
ゲーム機風のデザインもレトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない！？
Doesn't the game console design look cute and retro!?
はい！そしてフルセット特典はこちらです！
Alright! And here is the full set bonus!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドがつきます！
It comes with a cheki-style bromide drawn by Momoko-mama!
数量限定版は直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージ入り、
The limited edition has a handwritten signature and a foiled message...
通常版は箔押しの複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！
...while the regular edition has a foiled signature and message!
販売開始が、このあと21時10分に
Sales will start at 21:10, shortly after this...
してあるので、皆さんあの、慌てないで！大丈夫です！
...so everyone, please don't panic! It's okay!
10分からなので！はい！あの、見ていってください！よろしくお願いします！
It starts at 21:10! Yes! Please check it out! Thank you!
さらに特典ASMRボイスもつきます！
There's also a bonus ASMR voice!
毎年恒例の、君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃうASMRボイス2026年版！
The annual 2026 version of the ASMR voice where I celebrate your birthday instead!
こちらですね、毎年みんな誕生日まで我慢して聞いて「わーい！」ってなってるの
I'm so happy to see everyone wait until their birthday to listen to it and go "Yay!" every year.
すごく嬉しく思ってます！ぜひゲットしてください！
I'm really glad! Please be sure to get it!
はい！ということでね！
Alright! And with that!
怒涛のお知らせでしたが、
That was a lot of announcements,
可愛いでしょ？
but aren't they cute?
みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて、こよ嬉しいよ！
I'm so happy that everyone is saying they're cute!
表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ！にへ～！
My expressions have changed a bit too! Hehe~!
これが出来るようになりました！
I can do this now!
あとは、キリッ！
And also, sharp!
えーい！こんな表情も出来るようになりました！
Hyah! I can make these faces now too!
メン限をお楽しみに！
Look forward to the members-only live!
ということで今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026ゲームソングライブに見に来てくれて
So, thank you all for coming to the Hakuya Koyori Birthday Live 2026 Game Song Live today!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
このあとですね、新曲のアニメMV公開と
After this, the animated MV for my new song will be released...
メン限ライブ、あれですね、アニメMV公開見て
...and then the members-only live. Watch the MV release first...
で、10分からグッズ買って
...then buy the merch at 21:10...
15分からメン限ライブって感じでゆっくり順番に
...and then the members-only live at 21:15. You can take it one step at a time.
行けるようになっているので、慌てず、欠けず、なんだ
It's set up so you can go in order, so don't rush, don't miss out...
押さずでよろしくお願いします！
...and don't push! Thank you!
ということで今日はちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど
So, although we started a bit late today,
この3Dお披露目生誕ライブも出来て、大好きなゲームソングいっぱい披露できて
I'm glad we could do this 3D debut birthday live and perform so many of my favorite game songs!
嬉しかったよ！みんな本当に見に来てくれてありがとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you all so much for coming to watch!
また会おうね！ありがとう！
Let's meet again! Thank you!
MV見てね～！
Watch the MV, okay~!
ぽつり灯り 管制塔
A single point of light, the control tower
砂嵐の向こうへ
Towards the other side of the sandstorm
祈るように綴った
I wrote, as if in prayer,
これからのこと
Of the things yet to come
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
お便り 届いていますか
Has my letter reached you?
この世界がいつからか
Since some time ago, this world...
まるで他人事のように
...has felt like someone else's business
やけに静かなので
It's become so strangely quiet